<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PFTPproject</string>
    <string name="aboutus">PFTP is an online initiative whose mission is to support the vision of Prime Minister of Pakistan. This initiative is not just a training program but a revolution that will help generate employment and prepare Pakistan to run in the race of future of work around the world. We believe everyone should have the opportunity to create progress through technology and develop the skills of tomorrow with assessments, learning paths and courses authored by industry experts. Pakistan Freelancing Training Program (PFTP) has also been appraised by the Government of Pakistan to train the youth of Pakistan in the world of Information technology skill sets to shape the technical workforce for emerging technologies that will contribute to Pakistan’s economy, National Infrastructure security, and a dream of a digital and, prosperous Pakistan. Our vision is to reduce unemployment, creating awareness of 4.O and upcoming 5.O emerging technologies. Drive economic growth in Pakistan by increasing the inflow of foreign currency. After Learning this Program diligently, one can earn from $2000/- to $10000/- per month from international markets.
</string>
    <string name="contactus">In case of queries you can contact us at 0303-4321118 | 0318-4321118 email us at support@pftpedu.org</string>
<string name="faculty">1. All instructors/trainers will be responsible for providing all helping, learning and practice materials to the student and also to the management of PFTP.
 </string>
    <string name="two">2. Any misconduct, absence without intimation will be considered as the breach of contract and will be subjected to the legal sue through proper channel.</string>
<string name="three">3. PFTP will not allow any instructor to record his/her own lecture or lecture of other instructor by using voice recorder or video recorder at any stage of the course. Moreover if management fined such practice, they keep the right to take strict legal action against it. </string>
<string name="four">4. All instructors, irrespective of their location, occupation or nature are not supposed to prolonged courses whether online or offline, without the prior intimation to the higher management of PFTP. Any unnecessary delay or completion of course before the defined will result as the breach of contract. Also monetary terms will be considered accordingly by the higher management of PFTP.</string>
</resources>